https://inceptionvr.com/privacy-policy/

Privacy policy
IMPORTANT — THESE TERMS AND CONDITIONS (“AGREEMENT“) IS A LEGAL AGREEMENT BETWEEN YOU (EITHER AN INDIVIDUAL OR ENTITY) (“YOU” OR “YOUR“) AND INCEPTION VR, INC. (HEREINAFTER “COMPANY“, “WE“, “US” OR “OUR“) THAT SETS FORTH THE LEGAL TERMS AND CONDITIONS FOR YOUR USE OF WWW.INCEPTIONVR.COM AND ANY OTHER WEBSITE OWNED AND OPERATED BY COMPANY (THE “WEBSITE(S)“), INCLUDING ANY OF OUR SERVICES OFFERED THROUGH SUCH WEBSITES (THE “SERVICE(S)“).BY USING THE WEBSITES OR SERVICES, YOU AGREE TO THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF THIS AGREEMENT.
1INFORMATION WE COLLECTPERSONAL INFORMATION. WE MAY COLLECT INFORMATION THAT PERSONALLY IDENTIFIES YOU, SUCH AS YOUR NAME, USER NAME, EMAIL ADDRESS, LOCATION AND OTHER PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION WHEN YOU SIGN UP FOR THE WEBSITE OR SERVICES (“PERSONAL INFORMATION”). THE DECISION TO PROVIDE THIS INFORMATION IS OPTIONAL. HOWEVER, IF YOU CHOOSE NOT TO PROVIDE THE REQUESTED INFORMATION, YOU MAY NOT BE ABLE TO USE SOME OR ALL OF THE FEATURES OF THE WEBSITE OR SERVICES.
USAGE DATA AND WEBSITE ACTIVITY. WE AUTOMATICALLY COLLECT INFORMATION REGARDING THE ACTIONS YOU TAKE ON THE WEBSITE AND SERVICES (“USAGE DATA”). USAGE DATA IS INFORMATION OR CONTENT WE COLLECT ABOUT THE USE OF OUR WEBSITE OR SERVICES IN A WAY THAT DOES NOT IDENTIFY AN INDIVIDUAL USER. USAGE DATA HELPS US UNDERSTAND TRENDS IN OUR USERS’ NEEDS SO THAT WE CAN BETTER CONSIDER NEW FEATURES OR OTHERWISE TAILOR OR ENHANCE OUR SERVICES. THIS PRIVACY POLICY IN NO WAY RESTRICTS OR LIMITS OUR COLLECTION AND USE OF USAGE DATA, AND WE MAY SHARE USAGE DATA ABOUT OUR USERS WITH THIRD PARTIES FOR VARIOUS PURPOSES, INCLUDING TO HELP US BETTER UNDERSTAND OUR CUSTOMERS’ NEEDS AND IMPROVE OUR SERVICES. THIS MAY INCLUDE AUTOMATIC COLLECTION OF THE TYPE OF WEB BROWSER YOU USE, YOUR OPERATING SYSTEM, YOUR INTERNET SERVICE PROVIDER, YOUR IP ADDRESS, THE PAGES YOU VIEW, HOW YOU INTERACT WITH LINKS ON THE SERVICES, COMMENTS AND OTHER CONTENT YOU POST VIA THE SERVICES AND THE TIME AND DURATION OF YOUR VISITS TO THE WEBSITE. THIS USAGE DATA MAY BE ASSOCIATED WITH YOUR ACCOUNT (ONCE YOU SIGN UP TO OUR SERVICES), BUT WE DO NOT DISCLOSE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION TO THIRD PARTIES UNLESS OTHERWISE PROVIDED HEREIN. WE MAY STORE SUCH USAGE DATA AND/OR SUCH INFORMATION MAY BE INCLUDED IN DATABASES OWNED AND MAINTAINED BY COMPANY AFFILIATES, AGENTS OR SERVICE PROVIDERS. WE MAY USE SUCH INFORMATION AND POOL IT WITH OTHER INFORMATION TO TRACK, FOR EXAMPLE, THE TOTAL NUMBER OF VISITORS TO OUR WEBSITE/SERVICES, THE NUMBER OF VISITORS TO EACH PAGE OF OUR WEBSITE, ETC.
COOKIES AND WEB BEACONS. WE MAY USE COOKIES (A SMALL TEXT FILE PLACED ON YOUR COMPUTER TO IDENTIFY YOUR COMPUTER AND BROWSER). WE MAY ALSO USE WEB BEACONS (A FILE PLACED ON A WEBSITE THAT MONITORS USAGE). WE MAY USE COOKIES AND WEB BEACONS TO IMPROVE THE EXPERIENCE OF THE WEBSITE AND SERVICES, SUCH AS PRE-POPULATING YOUR USER NAME FOR EASIER LOGIN. WE DO NOT USE COOKIES OR WEB BEACONS TO COLLECT PERSONAL INFORMATION. MOST WEB BROWSERS ARE INITIALLY SET UP TO ACCEPT COOKIES. AT THIS TIME, OUR WEBSITE DOES NOT RECOGNIZE AUTOMATED BROWSER SIGNALS REGARDING TRACKING, OR “DO-NOT-TRACK” SIGNALS. YOU CAN REMOVE PERSISTENT COOKIES AND CHANGE YOUR PRIVACY PREFERENCES BY FOLLOWING DIRECTIONS PROVIDED IN YOUR INTERNET BROWSER’S “HELP” DIRECTORY. HOWEVER, CERTAIN FEATURES OF THE WEBSITE OR SERVICES MAY NOT WORK IF YOU DELETE OR DISABLE COOKIES. SOME OF OUR SERVICE PROVIDERS MAY USE THEIR OWN COOKIES AND WEB BEACONS IN CONNECTION WITH THE SERVICES THEY PERFORM ON OUR BEHALF, AS FURTHER EXPLAINED BELOW.
2HOW WE USE INFORMATION AND WHEN WE MAY SHARE AND DISCLOSE INFORMATION GENERALLY
WE MAY USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION FOR THE PURPOSE FOR WHICH IT WAS PROVIDED, INCLUDING WITHOUT LIMITATION FOR THE PURPOSES DESCRIBED FURTHER BELOW:
PROVISION AND MONITORING OF THE SERVICES: WE WILL USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION TO PROVIDE YOU WITH ACCESS TO AND TO SUPPORT YOUR USE OF THE SERVICES AND TO MONITOR YOUR USE OF THE SERVICES. WE MAY ALSO GIVE YOU THE OPPORTUNITY TO STORE, REVIEW AND EDIT PERSONAL INFORMATION AND OTHER INFORMATION ON THE WEBSITE.
SURVEYS, CONTESTS AND OTHER SPECIAL OFFERS: FROM TIME TO TIME, WE MAY OFFER OUR USERS THE OPPORTUNITY TO PARTICIPATE IN SURVEYS, CONTESTS AND OTHER SPECIAL OFFERS. IF YOU ELECT TO PARTICIPATE IN THESE SERVICES, YOU WILL NEED TO PROVIDE CERTAIN PERSONAL INFORMATION.[CONFIRM]QUESTIONS AND REQUESTS: IF YOU CONTACT US BY E-MAIL OR OTHERWISE, WE WILL USE THE PERSONAL INFORMATION YOU PROVIDE TO ANSWER YOUR QUESTION OR RESOLVE YOUR PROBLEM.
CONTACTING YOU ABOUT OTHER PRODUCTS, SERVICES AND EVENTS: IF YOU OPT-IN, COMPANY AND/OR THIRD PARTIES MAY USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION TO CONTACT YOU IN THE FUTURE TO TELL YOU ABOUT PRODUCTS, SERVICES AND EVENTS THAT MAY BE OF INTEREST TO YOU.
RESEARCH AND DATA ANALYSIS: IN AN ONGOING EFFORT TO BETTER UNDERSTAND AND SERVE THE USERS OF THE WEBSITE AND THE SERVICES, COMPANY MAY CONDUCT RESEARCH ON ITS CUSTOMERS’ DEMOGRAPHICS, INTERESTS AND BEHAVIOR BASED ON USAGE DATA AND OTHER INFORMATION PROVIDED TO US. THIS DATA MAY BE COMPILED AND ANALYZED ON AN AGGREGATE BASIS, AND COMPANY MAY SHARE THIS DATA WITH ADVERTISERS, RESEARCHERS, BUSINESS PARTNERS, PUBLICATIONS, AND OTHER THIRD PARTIES. THIS INFORMATION WILL NOT IDENTIFY YOU PERSONALLY.SERVICE IMPROVEMENT: WE MAY USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION, AGGREGATED PERSONAL INFORMATION AND OTHER NON-PERSONALLY-IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION COLLECTED THROUGH THE WEBSITE AND SERVICES TO HELP US IMPROVE THE CONTENT AND FUNCTIONALITY OF THE WEBSITE, TO BETTER UNDERSTAND OUR USERS AND TO IMPROVE THE SERVICES.
ORDER FULFILLMENT: IF YOU SIGN UP TO OUR SERVICES, WE MAY USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION THAT YOU PROVIDE TO FULFILL ANY ORDERS YOU MAY PLACE FOR SERVICES OFFERED BY COMPANY.
3INFORMATION YOU MAKE AVAILABLE TO OTHERSTHE WEBSITE MAY INCLUDE FEATURES FOR CREATION OF A PROFILE OR SUBMISSION OF PUBLIC QUERIES (LIKE CHATS, BLOG, OR OTHER COMMUNICATIONS FEATURES), YOU MAY MAKE CERTAIN OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION AVAILABLE TO OTHERS THROUGH SUCH FEATURES, SUCH AS YOUR NAME, YOUR USER NAME, AND YOUR PICTURE. THIS INFORMATION MAY BE ACCESSED BY USERS WHO USE THE WEBSITE OR SERVICES AND MAY BE ACCESSED BY COMMERCIAL SEARCH ENGINES SUCH AS GOOGLE, YAHOO!, AND BING TO THE EXTENT THAT SUCH ENGINES ARE PERMITTED TO ACCESS THE WEBSITE OR SERVICES. [DANA- NOT SURE THIS WOULD BE APPLICABLE TO THE WEBSITE BUT IT DOESN’T HURT TO HAVE IT HERE – LET ME KNOW IF YOU WISH TO REMOVE]
4THIRD PARTY SERVICES AND APPLICATIONSTHROUGH THE WEBSITE OR SERVICES, YOU MAY ELECT TO ACCESS THIRD-PARTY WEBSITES, SERVICES, APPLICATIONS AND SOCIAL NETWORKS. WHEN YOU DO SO, YOU MAY BE ABLE TO IMPORT INFORMATION FROM THOSE OTHER SERVICES AND APPLICATIONS AND SHARE CONTENT WITH THOSE SERVICES. WE ARE NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR SUCH THIRD PARTY’S SERVICES AND WEBSITES AND YOU SHOULD REVIEW THEIR PRIVACY POLICIES BEFORE SHARING YOUR INFORMATION ON SUCH SITES/ APPS. IF YOU ELECT TO ENABLE SUCH THIRD-PARTY SERVICES OR APPLICATIONS, THE INFORMATION YOU SHARE WITH SUCH THIRD-PARTY SERVICES AND APPLICATIONS WILL BE SUBJECT TO THEIR PRIVACY POLICIES AND YOUR PRIVACY SETTINGS. THIRD PARTIES MAY COLLECT, BUT WE DO NOT AUTHORIZE THEM TO COLLECT, PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION ABOUT YOUR ONLINE ACTIVITIES OVER TIME AND ACROSS DIFFERENT WEBSITES WHEN YOU USE THE WEBSITE OR SERVICES.
5SERVICE PROVIDERSFROM TIME TO TIME, WE MAY ESTABLISH A BUSINESS RELATIONSHIP WITH OTHER BUSINESSES THAT WE BELIEVE TO BE TRUSTWORTHY AND HAVE PRIVACY PRACTICES CONSISTENT WITH OURS (“SERVICE PROVIDERS”). FOR EXAMPLE, WE MAY CONTRACT WITH SERVICE PROVIDERS TO PROVIDE CERTAIN SERVICES, SUCH AS HOSTING AND MAINTENANCE, DATA STORAGE AND MANAGEMENT, AND MARKETING AND PROMOTIONS. WE ONLY PROVIDE OUR SERVICE PROVIDERS WITH THE INFORMATION NECESSARY FOR THEM TO PERFORM THESE SERVICES ON OUR BEHALF. EACH SERVICE PROVIDER MUST AGREE TO USE REASONABLE SECURITY PROCEDURES AND PRACTICES, APPROPRIATE TO THE NATURE OF THE INFORMATION INVOLVED, IN ORDER TO PROTECT YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION FROM UNAUTHORIZED ACCESS, USE OR DISCLOSURE. SERVICE PROVIDERS ARE PROHIBITED FROM USING PERSONAL INFORMATION OTHER THAN AS SPECIFIED BY COMPANY.
6ADVERTISINGWE MAY WORK WITH THIRD-PARTY ADVERTISERS, SEARCH PROVIDERS, AND AD NETWORKS (“ADVERTISERS”). THESE COMPANIES MAY COLLECT AND USE INFORMATION ABOUT YOUR USE OF THE WEBSITE OR SERVICES IN ORDER TO PROVIDE ADVERTISEMENTS ABOUT GOODS AND SERVICES THAT MAY BE OF INTEREST TO YOU. ADVERTISEMENTS MAY BE SHOWN VIA THE WEBSITE, THE SERVICES, OR THIRD-PARTY WEBSITES AND ONLINE SERVICES. THESE COMPANIES MAY PLACE OR RECOGNIZE A UNIQUE COOKIE ON YOUR COMPUTER OR USE OTHER TECHNOLOGIES SUCH AS WEB BEACONS. OUR PRIVACY POLICY DOES NOT COVER ANY USE OF INFORMATION THAT ADVERTISERS MAY COLLECT FROM YOU OR THAT YOU CHOOSE TO PROVIDE TO THEM.
7OTHER TRANSFERSWE MAY SHARE PERSONAL INFORMATION AND USAGE DATA WITH BUSINESSES CONTROLLING, CONTROLLED BY, OR UNDER COMMON CONTROL WITH COMPANY. IF COMPANY IS MERGED, ACQUIRED, OR SOLD, OR IN THE EVENT OF A TRANSFER OF SOME OR ALL OF OUR ASSETS OR EQUITY, WE MAY DISCLOSE OR TRANSFER PERSONAL INFORMATION AND USAGE DATA IN CONNECTION WITH SUCH TRANSACTION.
8COMPLIANCE WITH LAWS AND LAW ENFORCEMENTCOMPANY WILL COOPERATE WITH GOVERNMENT AND LAW ENFORCEMENT OFFICIALS AND PRIVATE PARTIES TO ENFORCE AND COMPLY WITH THE LAW. WE MAY DISCLOSE PERSONAL INFORMATION AND ANY OTHER CONTENT AND INFORMATION ABOUT YOU TO GOVERNMENT OR LAW ENFORCEMENT OFFICIALS OR PRIVATE PARTIES IF, IN OUR DISCRETION, WE BELIEVE IT IS NECESSARY OR APPROPRIATE IN ORDER TO RESPOND TO LEGAL REQUESTS (INCLUDING COURT ORDERS AND SUBPOENAS), TO PROTECT THE SAFETY, PROPERTY OR RIGHTS OF COMPANY OR OF ANY THIRD PARTY, TO PREVENT OR STOP ANY ILLEGAL, UNETHICAL, OR LEGALLY ACTIONABLE ACTIVITY, OR TO COMPLY WITH THE LAW.
9BE CAREFUL WHEN YOU SHARE INFORMATION WITH OTHERSPLEASE BE AWARE THAT WHENEVER YOU SHARE INFORMATION ON A PUBLICLY AVAILABLE PAGE OR ANY OTHER PUBLIC FORUM ON THE WEBSITE OR SERVICES, OTHERS MAY ACCESS THAT INFORMATION. IN ADDITION, PLEASE REMEMBER THAT WHEN YOU SHARE INFORMATION IN ANY OTHER COMMUNICATIONS WITH THIRD PARTIES, THAT INFORMATION MAY BE PASSED ALONG OR MADE PUBLIC BY OTHERS. THIS MEANS THAT ANYONE WITH ACCESS TO SUCH INFORMATION CAN POTENTIALLY USE IT FOR ANY PURPOSE, INCLUDING SENDING UNSOLICITED COMMUNICATIONS.
10EXCLUSIONSTHIS PRIVACY POLICY SHALL NOT APPLY TO ANY UNSOLICITED INFORMATION YOU PROVIDE TO COMPANY THROUGH THE WEBSITE OR SERVICES OR THROUGH ANY OTHER MEANS. THIS INCLUDES, BUT IS NOT LIMITED TO, INFORMATION POSTED TO ANY PUBLIC AREAS OF THE WEBSITE, SUCH AS BULLETIN BOARDS, ANY IDEAS FOR NEW PRODUCTS OR MODIFICATIONS TO EXISTING PRODUCTS, AND OTHER UNSOLICITED SUBMISSIONS (COLLECTIVELY, “UNSOLICITED INFORMATION”). ALL UNSOLICITED INFORMATION SHALL BE DEEMED TO BE NON-CONFIDENTIAL AND COMPANY SHALL BE FREE, AND YOU HEREBY GRANT COMPANY THE RIGHT, TO REPRODUCE, USE, DISCLOSE, AND DISTRIBUTE SUCH UNSOLICITED INFORMATION TO OTHERS WITHOUT LIMITATION OR ATTRIBUTION.
11SECURITYWE MAINTAIN PHYSICAL, ELECTRONIC, AND PROCEDURAL SAFEGUARDS TO PROTECT THE CONFIDENTIALITY AND SECURITY OF PERSONAL INFORMATION AND OTHER INFORMATION TRANSMITTED TO US. HOWEVER, NO DATA TRANSMISSION OVER THE INTERNET OR OTHER NETWORK CAN BE GUARANTEED TO BE 100% SECURE. AS A RESULT, WHILE WE STRIVE TO PROTECT INFORMATION TRANSMITTED ON OR THROUGH THE WEBSITE OR SERVICES, WE CANNOT AND DO NOT GUARANTEE THE SECURITY OF ANY INFORMATION YOU TRANSMIT ON OR THROUGH THE WEBSITE OR SERVICES, AND YOU DO SO AT YOUR OWN RISK.
12LINKSOUR WEBSITE AND SERVICES MAY CONTAIN LINKS OR INTEGRATE WITH OTHER WEBSITES AND ONLINE SERVICES, OR ALLOW OTHERS TO SEND YOU SUCH LINKS. COMPANY IS NOT RESPONSIBLE OR LIABLE FOR ANY DAMAGE OR LOSS RELATED TO YOUR USE OF ANY THIRD-PARTY WEBSITE OR ONLINE SERVICE. YOU SHOULD ALWAYS READ THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS AND PRIVACY POLICY OF A THIRD-PARTY WEBSITE OR ONLINE SERVICE BEFORE USING IT, WHETHER DIRECTLY OR IN CONNECTION WITH YOUR USE OF THE WEBSITE OR SERVICES.
13ADDITIONAL TERMSANY SOFTWARE, MOBILE APPLICATIONS, PRODUCTS, DEVICES OR OTHER SERVICES OFFERED BY COMPANY FROM TIME TO TIME (COLLECTIVELY “APP(S)”) ARE SUBJECT TO ADDITIONAL END USER LICENSE TERMS, RULES, POLICIES, AND PROCEDURES (COLLECTIVELY “ADDITIONAL TERMS”). WHERE ADDITIONAL TERMS APPLY, WE WILL MAKE THEM AVAILABLE FOR YOU IN CONNECTION WITH YOUR USE OF SUCH APPS.
14CHILDREN'S PRIVACYWE DO NOT KNOWINGLY COLLECT PERSONAL INFORMATION FROM CHILDREN UNDER THE AGE OF 13. IF WE BECOME AWARE THAT WE HAVE INADVERTENTLY RECEIVED PERSONAL INFORMATION FROM A CHILD UNDER THE AGE OF 13, WE WILL DELETE SUCH INFORMATION FROM OUR RECORDS.
15APPLICABLE LAW; PROCESSING IN OTHER COUNTRIESPLEASE BE AWARE THAT YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION AND COMMUNICATIONS MAY BE TRANSFERRED TO AND MAINTAINED ON SERVERS OR DATABASES LOCATED OUTSIDE YOUR STATE, PROVINCE, OR COUNTRY. BY USING OUR WEBSITE OR SERVICES, YOU AGREE THAT THE APPLICABLE LAWS OF THE STATE OF DELAWARE WILL GOVERN THE COLLECTION, USE, TRANSFER, AND DISCLOSURE OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION AND COMMUNICATIONS. THE LAWS OF DELAWARE MAY NOT BE AS PROTECTIVE OF YOUR PRIVACY AS THOSE IN YOUR LOCATION.
16PRIVACY POLICY CHANGESFROM TIME TO TIME, WE MAY CHANGE THIS PRIVACY POLICY. IF WE CHANGE THIS PRIVACY POLICY, WE WILL GIVE YOU NOTICE BY POSTING THE REVISED PRIVACY POLICY ON THE WEBSITE. THOSE CHANGES WILL GO INTO EFFECT ON THE EFFECTIVE DATE SHOWN IN THE REVISED PRIVACY POLICY. BY CONTINUING TO USE THE WEBSITE OR SERVICES, YOU CONSENT TO THE REVISED PRIVACY POLICY.
17MANAGING YOUR INFORMATION PREFERENCESIF YOU PROVIDE US YOUR EMAIL OR OTHER CONTACT INFORMATION, WE MAY SEND YOU VARIOUS NOTIFICATIONS, INCLUDING MARKETING OR PROMOTIONAL MATERIALS. YOU CAN OPT OUT OF RECEIVING CERTAIN EMAILS BY CLICKING THE UNSUBSCRIBE LINK PROVIDED IN AN EMAIL, OR BY EMAILING US AT INFO@INCEPTIONVR.COM.
18CONTACTIF YOU HAVE QUESTIONS OR CONCERNS REGARDING THIS PRIVACY POLICY, PLEASE EMAIL US AT INFO@INCEPTIONVR.COM.
